[{"answer": "Not really, no.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "Well, don't you think as a host, if I say this is what I want to talk about, that's what we should address?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "I'm doing well.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "Christine O'Donnell, how are you?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "You can be both, can't you?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Well, I think -- I like the way you say it's a hiccup.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "When you look back on it, what was the catalyst, do you think, or -- not your down fall but your hiccup?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Because I dabbled into witchcraft.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "How can you be a witch?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "Your first date was in the satanic altar?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "Well, I hope to stay in the political arena -- maybe not necessarily as a candidate or in an elected office.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "I would have thought there was a pretty good chance that you could make a pretty big move back into the political stage, isn't it?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "The problem, Christine, if I may just jump in there?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Let's not even go there.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Do you still think masturbation is wrong?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Well, I am a practicing Catholic and I support what the Catholic Church teaches.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "So, am I right in assuming your views have evolved over the years?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "Let's not even go there.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Can I ask you, have you -- have you committed lust in your heart and therefore adultery?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "I address that stuff in the book.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "-- what is your view of gay marriage, for example?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "-- I obviously want to talk about the issues that I choose to talk about in the book.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "I talk about my religious beliefs, yes.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "Do you answer that question in the book?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Because I don't think it's relevant.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "So, I'm bemused as to why you wouldn't just say it in an interview if it's in the book?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "I'm not talking policies.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "You should restore that?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "I'm not being weird about this, Piers.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "Why are you being so weird about this?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Not really, no.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "Well, don't you think as a host, if I say this is what I want to talk about, that's what we should address?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "Well, I was supposed to be speaking at the Republican women's club at 6:00, and I chose to be a little late for that not to be -- you know, yes, not to endure rude talk show hosts, but to talk to you about my book and to talk about the issues that I address in my book.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "You're leaving?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "Yes, but these issues are in your book.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Have you read the book?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "He's still there.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "Are we done?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "Well, I wouldn't characterize it as aggressive when you consider the sense of urgency that I think we all need to have about the crisis of confidence that exists in our country as a result of a crisis of leadership.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "What do you hope to achieve here?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Well, I think unfortunately the gap between the rich and poor, and the haves and have nots has widened.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "So there's a real disparity here between I think big, successful companies like yours, like McDonald's, like Apple and so on, and what is happening to the average guy on the street, isn't there?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "Well, the irony is when I came back in 2008, it was terrible timing because it was during the cataclysmic financial crisis.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "Tell me about that period and about what you did to get Starbucks back on fire again?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "First off, I want to be extremely respectful of Congress and the president.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "What parallels do you see with America incorporated?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "You're doing your homework.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "I have spies everywhere.", "docId": "110817pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "But I didn't know -- how did you find that out about the China Club?", "qSentId": 450}]